mochigames.com 2010-12-31

# Privacy - MochiGames

### MochiGames Privacy Policy

Mochi Media, Inc. (“Mochi”) knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting Mochi’s MochiGames website at http://www.mochigames.com, (the “Website”), or using any of our services offered through the Website (including but not limited to MochiCoins), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

#### What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers Mochi’s treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that Mochi gathers when you are accessing the Website and when you use our services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Mochi does not own or control, or to individuals that Mochi does not employ or manage. 

#### What Personal Information Does MochiGames display or Collect?

The information we gather from users enables us to personalize and improve our services, and to allow our users to set up a user account and profile that can be used to interact with other users through the Website. In connection with the Website, we request and display some personal information to other users and visitors of the Website, which allows users to identify each other. 

We collect the following types of information from our users.

#### Personal Information You Provide to Us:

We receive and store any information you enter on the Website or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected include: 

  * Profile: Username; email; password; gender; birthday; some email settings; avatar pic; 
  * Your Social Networking Information: information collected from social networks to which you belong (e.g. Facebook; Twitter; etc.) in accordance with your providing us with your credentials and permission; or information posted to any such social networks through your MochiGames account. 

You may choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as keeping a high score record, responding to your requests for certain information, products and services, customizing the advertising and content you see, and communicating with you about specials and new features. You may modify or remove any of your personal information at any time by logging into your account and accessing features to edit your profile and account information. 

#### Personal Information Collected Automatically:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Website or obtain services from us, including, but not limited to the following: 

  * Game playing data: While you are logged into your MochiGames account, we keep track of the games you play; when you played them; the sites where you played them; and general game activity including in-game communications. 
  * MochiCoins and Wallet: We collect billing information in order to fund your MochiGames Wallet and we record your MochiCoins transactions. 

Mochi automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Mochi cookie information, and the page you requested. We also record the details of your transactions on the Website. 

Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. Mochi only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often users use parts of the Website so that we can make the Website appealing to as many users as possible. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our users, collectively, use our site. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their services and the Website, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience. Again, Mochi never discloses aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally. 

#### E-mail Communications:

We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from Mochi if your computer supports this type of program. Mochi uses this confirmation to help us make e-mails more interesting and helpful. 

#### What About Cookies?

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. Mochi cookies do not collect Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is. 
  * Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of the Website’s most attractive features. 
  * Ads appearing on the Website may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Mochi and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

#### Will MochiGames Share Any of the Personal Information it Receives?

Personal Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only as described below. 

Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control:
     We anticipate that we may become affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses may operate stores at the Website or sell items to you through the Website. In other situations, Mochi may provide services, or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, and we will share user information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business. 
Agents:
     We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples include sending email, analyzing data, and providing user services. Unless we tell you differently, Mochi’s agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes. 
User profiles:
     User profile information including users’ MochiGames ID may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Website. Users’ full names will not be directly revealed to other users by Mochi. Any information you post to public areas (such as forums) will be generally publicly available and associated with your MochiGames ID. 
Promotional Offers:
     We may send offers to certain users on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please send us an email to support@mochigames.com with the subject heading “Unsubscribe Request”. 
Business Transfers:
     In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Mochi, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Mochi goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of Mochi may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy. 
Protection of MochiGames and Others:
     We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Mochi, our employees, our users, or others. This includes, without limitation, exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. 
With Your Consent:
     Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be given the option to prevent the sharing of this information. 

#### Is Personal Information About me Secure?

Your Mochi account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need ensure unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

Mochi endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private, however, Mochi cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time. For additional information about the security measures Mochi uses in connection with the Website, please contact us at support@mochigames.com. 

The Website contains links to other sites. Mochi is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. This Privacy Policy only governs information collected on the Website. 

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post information to public areas on the Website or any other public forums, such information can be accessed by the public. 

#### What Personal Information Can I Access?

Mochi allows you to access the information about yourself in your profile for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. You may login to your profile to access your personal information at any time. 

#### What Other Choices Do I Have?

  * As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain Mochi features. 
  * You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the “What Personal Information Can I Access” section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. 
  * You may request deactivation of your account and deletion of personally identifiable information in your Mochi account by sending an e-mail to our webmaster at support@mochigames.com with the subject heading “Deletion Request.” Please note that when your personally identifiable information is deleted we no longer have the availability to send you information or payments. Additionally, some of your information may remain in our records after deactivation of your account. 
  * Mochi may use a user’s e-mail address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the Website or Mochi services. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. 

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Mochi may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used or collected. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you via e-mail or by posting an announcement on the Website. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after such changes have been first posted. 

#### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at the Website, please send us a detailed message to support@mochigames.com.
